JOHN BRINK

STUDENT IN INTERACTIVE MEDIA TECHNOLOGY



CONTACT INFORMATION

- +46 70 65 250 88
- john-brink@hotmail.com
- https://johnbrink.netlify.app
- in John Brink
- j<u>ohnbri</u>

COMPETENCES

••••	React.js	••••
••••	Wordpress	••••
••••	Unity	••••
••••	Python	••••
••••	C#	••••
••••	Java	••••
	••••	Wordpress Unity Python C#

LANGUAGES

Swedish
English
French

PROFILE

As a student in interactive media technology, I have developed skills for researching, creating, and evaluating digital products with a focus on human-computer interaction. My current goals are to build my knowledge in web development and UX design to a professional level. People often describe me as creative, open-minded, down-to-earth, responsible, calm, just to name a few.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

M.Sc. in Engineering - Interactive Media Technology KTH ROYAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, STOCKHOLM AUG 2018 - PRESENT (GRADUATING JUN 2023)

Summer course - Web Management

LINNAEUS UNIVERSITY, VÄXJÖ JUNE 2020 - AUG 2020

Upper Secondary School - Sustainable Technology

BROMANGYMANSIET, HUDIKSVALL AUG 2014 - JUN 2017

POSITIONS OF TRUST

Chapter of Media Technology, Stockholm

AUG 2018 - SEP 2021

- Project manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag
- Account manager of the career fair Medias Branschdag
- Event planner of yearly ski trip
- Event manager of Student Reception, twice
- Art director of the communications board

WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesperson

CIRCLE K, MÄRSTA AND HUDIKSVALL MAY 2017 – DEC 2017

- Retail salesperson at two different stations
- Cooked fast food for customers
- Was private chauffeur to business customers
- Managed car rental and washing services

Consultant

2COMPLETE, STOCKHOLM MAR 2019 - MAY 2019

- Seasonal work at a tire washing station
- Organized and washed tires
- Transported tires in a small truck to other stations